What network would you say is the worst, if I could ask?
Oh, man, that's a real tight spot.
Honestly, it's a simple question.
There's a lot of people in this pool.
And I would say, I'm not talking about Fox.
I'm not talking about Newsmax or any outlet that resembles them.
So I'll let you guys put the pieces together
on who I'm exactly talking about.
Who would you say, which network would you say?
MSNBC, for sure.
Oh, they're terrible.
I agree.
CNN, probably close.
Yeah, I'd rate it that way, MSNBC.
Brian Roberts, that he allows that to happen is a disgrace.
And CNN is second.
I would say CNN is not quite as bad as MS.
MSNBC is not really a news site anymore.
Oh, MSNBC is sick.
They're sick.
Sir, it's also just the stories that they publish
about what's the ICE enforcement operations that
are so heavily slanted that it's no longer, as I was saying,
no longer just Antifa, but Americans that
are becoming radicalized.
So they've been very irresponsible with how
they've been reporting on this.
MSNBC, for example, they're-
Would you rate them the worst?
Probably.
Who would you rate second?
Well, they ran a story about an operation in Southern California
about how a father of three Marines was arrested.
And they made it seem like they just did it because he's brown.
But there's video of that same man charging at the agents
with a weed whacker.
Now, I've worked with weed whackers back in the day.
And you don't want to be in the receiving end of one of those.
So that's why he was arrested.
But the story was presented as if it's a brown guy just
simply being arrested.
And I've been around ICE agents.
And I'm a citizen.
So I feel fine.
But it's just that's why.
It's not just Antifa.
It's not happening in a vacuum.
It's multiple factors.
No, it's working in conjunction.
I think they work in conjunction with some of the media.
I think ABC is very bad.
I think NBC is very bad.
And CBS has a new owner.
So we have hope for CBS.
CBS has a great new owner, my opinion.
But I will tell you, ABC is terrible.
NBC is terrible.
NBC is MSNBC, too.
They changed it.
They moved it over legally so they couldn't be
tainted by the words MSNBC.
But they are absolutely terrible.
There are a lot of them.
What about independents?